# MARCOS LÓPEZ SAPITRI CV



## **CONTACT**

- Email: marcoslopezsapitri.123@gmail.com

- Contact Page: Linktr.ee

- My Portfolio: My Portfolio - WEB

- Certificates: One Drive

#### INTRODUCTION

My name is Marcos Lopez Sapitri, a 27-year-old Spanish/Indonesian with diverse cultural insights. I am currently fully available for work.

I have solid experience and skills in Social Media Management, SEO and SEM Marketing, Tourism, Hospitality, Logistics, Public Relations, Event Planning, and Sales. I'm also eager to take on new challenges and grow professionally.

I am fluent in four languages: Spanish, English, Indonesian, and Javanese, and I have working knowledge of French, Italian, and Portuguese.

## **EXPERIENCE**

**Freelance** - Affiliate Marketing & Blogger (Personal Brand & Niche)

Actual 2024

Nueva Idea Mkt (Spanish) - Content & Leads Management
Actual 2024

Bamboo Oasis Resort, Bali, Indonesia - Accounts and Channels Coordinator

April 2024 – August 2024

Yonaguni Fiesta, Bali, Indonesia - Brand Ambassador in Bali February & November 2023

## Jepara Garden Resort, Jepara, Ind - Front Office HR

February 2021- April 2021

**Big K Hostel, Karimunjawa, Ind -** *Growth Hotel Marketing.* 

September 2020-December 2020

M.R.X Group (Freelance), Jakarta, Ind - Event Marketing Planner.

October 2018- February 2019

Kuehne+Nagel B.V. Zaandam, NL - Warehouse Operator.

April 2022 - December 2022

Ingram Micro Commerce & Lifecycle Services (de Bijenkorf), Tilburg, The Netherlands - Smart

Inbound/Picking/Shop Vas Warehouse Operator
May 2021- October 2021

Blue Coral Homestay, Karimunjawa, Indonesia - Operational Manager

April 2018-December 2020

#### **EDUCATION**

IES Adeje , Spain - School Certificate
May 2014

HTML 5 Course - udemy.com / Teacher : Víctor Robles
February 2023

SEO and WEB Positioning Course - udemy.com / Teacher: Jorge Jaramillo January 2024

**Excel (Microsoft) complete course** - *udemy.com / Teacher: Miguel Maraby*June 2021

CSS and CSS3 standard: Responsive, SASS, Flexbox, Grid and Bootstrap -

udemy.com / Teacher: Víctor Robles

March 2024

Marketing Strategies and Digital Marketing - udemy.com / Teacher: Andres Brachetta & Belén Rodríguez

March 2024

Instagram Specialist - udemy.com / Teacher: Federico Rodríguez

August 2024

# **SKILLS / ABILITIES**

- UPDATED MARKETING STRATEGIES (MARKETING MIX, SMART OBJECTIVES, AIDA METHOD, ETC...)
- KEYWORDS ANALYSIS AND STRATEGY (SHORT-TAIL VS LONG-TAIL STRATEGY, KWFINDER, ETC...)

- SEO AND WEB POSITIONING SPECIALIST (GOOGLE ALGORITM, SITEMAPS, AMP LANDING PAGES DESIGN ETC...)
- SOCIAL MEDIA CONTENT MANAGEMENT & CAMPAIGNS (META.BS [INSTAGRAM & FACEBOOK],
   YOUTUBE FOR CREATORS, INSIGHTS/ENGAMENT ANALYSIS, ETC...)
- HTML 5 (UPDATED STANDARD AND SEO ORIENTED)
- CSS3: RESPONSIVE DESIGN, SASS, FLEXBOX, GRID, BOOTSTRAP
- EXCEL/SHEETS, WORD/DOCS, POWERPOINT/SLIDES (BOTH MICROSOFT AND GOOGLE)
- CANVA (PRODUCT PRESENTATIONS, SOCIAL MEDIA POSTS, LOGOS, VIDEO EDITING)
- MICROSOFT CLIPCHAMP AND CAPCUT (VIDEO EDITING)
- OTA (ONLINE TRAVEL AGENT) & CHANNEL MANAGER SOFTWARE SYSTEM.
- CHAT GPT, DALL.E, GEMINI, M.COPILOT GOOGLE COLLAB, STABLE DIFUSSION XL (AI IMAGE PROCESSING AND PROMPTING)
- GOOGLE TRENDS, GOOGLE ANALYTICS & GOOGLE ADS
- NOTION AND GOOGLE CALENDAR (CONTENT PLANNING, ORGANIZING EVENTS, ARRANGE MEETINGS, ETC...)
- LANGUAGES: SPANISH, ENGLISH, INDONESIAN